in form
在形式上
has been deleted
已被删除
But when he found the technical department
但当他找到技术部时
When a listening device is discovered
当发现窃听设备时
stopped
已停止
There is no way to find the source
没有办法找到源头
Spies use Fang Yongping
间谍利用方永平
Chen Ting was also allowed to collude with Cheng Guoxian
还让陈挺与程国贤勾结
in the secret part
在秘密部分
They used the same method
他们用了同样的方法
In order to obtain a large amount of inside information
为了获取大量内幕信息
Confidential information within the company
公司内部机密信息
According to Chen Ting
据陈婷介绍
Mr. Zhang’s new goal
张先生的新目标
This is an international auction of High รถไฟ collection
这是High รถไฟ藏品的国际拍卖会
tell me in detail
详细告诉我
auction mode
拍卖模式
Kingdom plans high-speed rail repairs
王国计划高铁修理
Find partners around the world
在世界范围内寻找合作伙伴
include
包括
from four countries
来自四个国家
high train set
高火车组
He will attend the auction
他将参加拍卖会
Participate in the Rise of Trillions
参与万亿崛起
As for the Gimhae subway train set
至于金海地铁列车组
This is the fiercest competition
这是最激烈的竞争
Although Fang Yongping was arrested
方永平虽然被抓了
High-speed rail group internal surveillance video
高铁组内部监控视频
deleted
已删除
but i don't think so
但我不这么认为
That night of fog
那一夜的雾
give up easily
轻易放弃
There won't be just one way
不会只有一种方法
suggestion
建议
Pay more attention
要多加注意
in game
在游戏里
some news
一些新闻
About the auction
关于拍卖
Beware of taking advantage of them
谨防利用他们
by stealing this game
通过盗取这个游戏
you will still be a stone
你将依然是石头
in private matches
在私人比赛中
looking for some evidence
寻找一些证据
agree
同意
we must follow
我们必须遵循
high train set exercise
高火车组运动
Especially before the auction ends
尤其是在拍卖结束之前
To prevent criminals
为了防止犯罪分子
their secret moves
他们的秘密动作
Protect the integrity of the national economy
保护国民经济的完整性
What about other evidence?
其他证据呢？
How is this going
这是怎么回事
mysterious woman
神秘的女人
little evidence
证据很少
No progress yet
暂时没有进展
I have
我有
have some wheels
有一些轮子
This person has
此人有
Very high driving skills
非常高的驾驶技术
I fought with him twice
我和他打过两次仗
He rides a modified car
他骑的是一辆改装车
Where the signal disappears
信号消失的位置
The car workshop has been transformed
汽车车间已改造
in a car club
在汽车俱乐部里
Either a coach
要么是教练
Or a modding expert
要么是改装专家
Just check information
仅核对信息
very difficult
非常困难
so i ask
所以我问
Enter the club
进入俱乐部
for covert investigations
用于秘密调查
This way we can arrest the suspect as quickly as possible
这样我们就能尽快逮捕犯罪嫌疑人
No matter what identity you enter
无论您输入什么身份
member
成员
Did you fight with him?
你和他打架了吗？
Will he know?
他会知道吗？
The last time I chased Han Ji
上次追韩吉的时候
I fought with him
我和他打了
But we all wear helmets
但我们都带着头盔
We kept a certain distance
我们保持了一定的距离
I think you don't know me
我认为你不认识我
but
但
No, but
不是，但
I know him best
我最了解他
There is no better choice than me
没有比我更好的选择
no no no
不不不
behind them
在他们后面
negative investigations like this
像这样的负面调查
you have to take initiative
你必须采取主动
He made Wu Xi move
他让吴曦动了
In order to find the suspect as soon as possible
为了尽快找到嫌疑人
but
但
You must do good things before doing things
做事之前你必须先做好事
completely
完全
Preparation
准备工作
Understood
明白了
I already have this thing
这东西我已经有了
Startup plan
启动计划
What's the plan?
计划是什么？
let's go
我们走吧
they agree
他们同意
let me go in again
让我再进去一次
There is no one here
这里没有人
when we last met
当我们上次见面时
when we start working
当我们开始工作时
But look now
但现在看看
nothing left
没有什么东西留下
what will you do?
你会怎么做？
should be closed during investigation
调查期间应关闭
After opening
打开后
I don’t know how many years it’s been
不知道多少年了
I'm very hardworking
我很努力
Unfortunately
很遗憾
Why did I see that?
为什么我看到了？
you are sadder than me
你比我更悲伤
i can understand how you feel
我能理解你的感受
at the beginning
在一开始的时候
I'm not used to this
我不习惯这样
but now
但现在
i feel very comfortable
我感到很自在
Don't I have any doubts?
我没有怀疑吗？
I never doubted her before
我以前从未怀疑过她
I doubt
我怀疑
but now i remember
但现在我记得
then
当时
I avoided it on purpose
我是故意回避的
if you were
如果你当时
I didn't ask you to investigate
我没让你调查
can he
他可以吗
I think sooner or later
我想迟早
a matter of time
时间问题
Do you regret it?
你后悔吗？
do not regret
不要后悔
actually i was thinking
其实我在想
meaning of my life
我生命的意义
what is it?
它是什么？
when i die
当我死的时候
No matter how much money there is
不管有多少钱
Regardless of fame and reputation
不论名气和声誉
I can't stand it
我受不了
so i came here
所以我来到了这里
try it
尝试一下
Was the experience good or bad?
体验是好是坏
So I have no regrets
所以我无怨无悔
One more interesting thing
还有一件有趣的事
I think
我想
I'm in Tianhai
我在天海
Located in Tianhai
位于天海
every day
每天
they want to know me
他们想了解我
But when something happened to my father
但当我父亲出了什么事
these friends
这些朋友
They disappeared for no reason
他们无缘无故消失了
I'm here
我在这
Yes
是的
You are just bold and not afraid of death
你只是大胆，不怕死
There's something I want to tell you
有件事我想告诉你
in the past
在过去
I've never felt like this
我从未有过这样的感觉
This spy organization is scary
这个间谍组织很可怕
when i wake up
当我醒来时
I find
我发现
for their goals
为了他们的目标
Yes
是的
they are more terrifying
他们更可怕
exceeded our expectations
超出我们的预期
Yes
是的
so
所以
you must protect yourself
你必须保护自己
Understood
明白了
correct
正确的
What will you do in the future?
未来你会做什么？
keep going
继续前进
I think
我想
I have to rely on my efforts
我要靠我的努力
Achieve financial freedom
实现财富自由
finally i found
最后我发现
he didn't get rid of my father
他没有摆脱我的父亲
Now
现在
This road must be walked alone
这条路必须一个人走
OK
好的
under any circumstances
任何状况之下
If you need help in the future
如果您将来需要帮助
call me anytime
随时给我打电话
Don't worry
不用担心
I also want to see
我也想看
I will rely on myself
我会靠我自己
How far can you reach?
你能达到多远？
this museum
这个博物馆
opening day
开幕当天
I will definitely come
我一定会来
this invitation letter
这份邀请函
certainly
当然
as soon as possible
尽快地
Do you want coffee?
你想要咖啡吗？
I just want a drink
我只想要一杯
OK
好的
Yaoyao is a good girl
瑶瑶是个好女孩
You must be kind to her
你一定要善待她
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Actually I've always wanted to tell you
其实我一直想告诉你
We are all
我们都是
Did not happen
没有发生
bring your coffee
带上你的咖啡
Hello
你好
Who are you
你是谁
I
我
Jihai Biotechnology Group Human Resources Department
集海生物集团人事部
we have received
我们已经收到
Resume you have sent
您已发送的简历
I'll inform you now
我现在就通知你
Next Wednesday at 9:30 a.m.
下周三早上九点半
interview
采访
Understood
明白了
He received Huang Ziqing
他接待了黄自清
from a group of animals
来自一群动物
Let him play spy
就让他扮演间谍吧
we can follow the evidence
我们可以追踪证据
Go find the people behind
去寻找后面的人
I think this is
我觉得这就是
not that simple
没那么简单
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
After Shi Li was arrested
石莉被捕后
we will complete
我们将完成
But in Macau
但在澳门
in Macau
在澳门
this spy
这个间谍
Why does he know?
他为什么知道？
About Huang Gaming’s whereabouts
关于Huang Gaming的行踪
I'm afraid ordinary people
恐怕普通人
they won't understand
他们不会明白的
And Dr. Feng
还有冯博士
makes no sense to me
对我没意义
Author: Shi Li
作者：石莉
But the spy knows
但间谍知道
After visiting Dr. Feng
拜访冯医生后
after his visit
他来访后
This type of flag indicates
此类标志表示
you mean?
你的意思是？
People with night fog belong to the animal group
有夜雾的人属于动物组
She's a spy, always ready
她是一名间谍，时刻准备着
This is good
这很好
Use this opportunity
利用这个机会
In order to let Huang Zicheng in
为了让黄子成进去
in
里面
I think you
我觉得你
You should believe Huang Zicheng
你应该相信黄子成
I just don't want to
我只是不想
Be the next Fang Lu
成为下一个方璐
I asked the commander
我问指挥官
Huang Zicheng
黄子成
You are responsible
你负责
I'll go to the club to investigate secretly
我去俱乐部秘密调查一下
I can't always communicate with him
我总是无法和他沟通
As for your relationship
至于你们之间的关系
It's more useful to hide it
隐藏起来更有用
The leader said
领导说
You are the most suitable person to replace me
你是最适合代替我的人
but now
但现在
The only thing that worries me is
唯一让我担心的是
Maybe that's it
正是这样也许
He does not accept your education
他不接受你的教育
Don't irritate me with these words
别用这些话激怒我
he doesn't accept
他不接受
I'll let him out immediately
我会立刻让他出来
this is amazing
这真太了不起了
we agree
我们同意
but remember
但要记住
you two
你们俩
never quarrel
从不吵架
Please ask Principal Gao
请高校长
Have you made arrangements?
你安排好了吗？
Are the arrangements made?
安排好了吗？
nature
自然
Do you need help?
你需要帮助吗？
no need
没有必要
Huang Zicheng looked at
黄子成看着
To Lu Feng
给陆峰
it has huge impact
它有巨大的影响
Calm down
冷静一点
how your brother feels
你哥哥的感受
Emotionally
情感上
you should do this
你应该这样做
Why do I feel like your brother?
为什么我感觉像你弟弟？
I've never seen him before
我以前从没见过他
You used to be so cute
以前的你好可爱
I'm always nice, okay?
我总是很好的，好吗？
really
确实
nature
自然
never found
从未发现
What's wrong with you, sad man?
你怎么了，悲伤的人？
I have a new task
我有新任务
I thought you would be excited
我以为你会很兴奋
I met Fang Lu
我遇见了方璐
I went to the art museum
我去了艺术博物馆
Do you feel sick?
你觉得不舒服吗？
I said I did it
我说我做到了
What's this?
这是什么？
He treats me like a brother
他待我如兄弟
but i hurt her
但我伤害了她
It can be said to be an abandoned family
可以说是一个被遗弃的家庭
And the most annoying thing is
而最烦人的是
i can't say anything
我什么也不能说
with my personality
以我的个性
I am sure
我肯定
I admit it directly
我直接承认
but this time
但这一次
I can't say a word
我一句话也说不出来
not just that
不只是这样
i have to pretend
我必须假装
I do not know anything
我什么都不知道
Where is Fang Lu?
方璐呢？
people
人民
He told me to get out as soon as possible
他叫我尽快出去
avoid
避免
just like his life
就像他的生活一样
this is not your fault
这不是你的错
And it's not Feng Lu's fault
而且这也不是冯璐的错
Know
知道
That's what those bastards in the night fog do
那些夜雾里的混蛋就是这么做的
but in my heart
但在我心里
i feel guilty
我感到内疚
Now you know the score
现在你知道比分了
if i let you
如果我让你
Select again
再次选择
Are you still doing this?
你还在这样做吗？
Yes
是的
in my heart
在我心里
So uncomfortable
真不舒服
This is it
就是这个
what you have to face
你必须面对的
The truth is more terrifying
真相更可怕
exceeded my expectations
超出我的预期
if you are not careful
如果你不小心的话
he lost his family
他失去了家人
do you want to withdraw
你想撤回
what will happen
会怎么样
whenever you see
每当你看到
harsh realism
严酷的现实主义
the more insistent you are
你越坚持
I don’t want Lao Huang
我不要老黄
He also faced this kind of thing
他也面临这样的事情
There are other threats
还有其他人威胁
presentable
体面的
Your sister is still worried about you
你姐姐还是担心你
Weak again
又弱了
become
变得
Why don't you come yourself?
你自己怎么不来？
let me
让我
You let me tell you
你让我告诉你
What?
什么？
i did well
我做得很好
why does it look like
为什么看起来
disloyal
不忠
Did you say that?
你这么说了吗？
this is acceptable
这是可以接受的
We're going to work soon
我们马上就要上班了
What do you do from nine to five in the morning?
早上九点到五点做什么
Did you fail?
你没通过吗？
interviewing
采访中
Maybe you can't get in
也许你进不去
Can you not give it to me?
可以不给我吗？
back off
退后
if you have confidence
如果你有信心
You won't come to your uncle.
你不会来找你叔叔的。
Can your uncle save me?
你叔叔能救我吗？
My uncle is back.
我叔叔回来了。
what happened?
发生了什么？
i lost my job
我失去了工作
I think
我想
fail for you
为你失败
Isn't this normal?
这不是很正常吗？
I'll go see what's on offer
我去看看有什么菜
I'll cook for you
我给你做饭
What’s wrong with you?
你怎么了？
I want to find a job
我想找工作
Where do I work?
我在哪里工作？
How is your company?
你们公司怎么样？
Where
在哪里
Me too
我也是
I should hug you too
我也应该拥抱你
daddy's legs
爸爸的腿
are you kidding
你在开玩笑吧
Does your company not recruit female employees?
你们公司不招女员工吗？
I have sent my resume
我已发送简历
Tian Yang
田阳
do you know
你知道吗
I just learned
我刚学到
Why
为什么
Sudden
突然
I believe
我相信
Not always reliable abroad
在国外并不总是可靠的
suddenly want to settle down
突然想安定下来
in my impression
在我的印象里
you work all day
你整天工作
she has never taken a class before
她以前从未上过课
People will always grow old
人总会变老
Isn't it, Dad?
不是吗，爸爸？
I said no
我说不
find another job
找另一份工作
You are not suitable for our company
你不适合我们公司
Why are you so old?
你怎么这么老了？
that person
那个人
he wants stability
他想要稳定
Isn't this a good thing?
这不是一件好事吗？
the word stability
稳定性这个词
you have nothing to do with it
你与它无关
You are suitable for fooling around
你适合胡闹
Understood
明白了
What if you come to me?
如果你来找我怎么办？
you brought me trouble
你给我带来了麻烦
I think it's best to forget it
我认为最好忘记它
"Gao Tianyang."
“高天阳。”
Is he my father?
他是我的父亲吗？
my uncle
我的叔叔
I believe
我相信
you have to support him
你必须支持他
in your company
在你们公司
Better than flying abroad
比坐国外飞机还好
Look what my brother said
看看我哥说的
how old are you?
你今年多大？
Almost thirty
快三十了
Physical strength, mental strength, hand speed
体力、脑力、手速
I can not
我不能
You are in the game world
你在游戏的世界里
in the game world
在游戏的世界里
I could just be the internet administrator
我可以只是互联网管理员
listen
听
pitiful
可怜的
yes dad
是的，爸爸
I'm so poor
我好穷
you should?
你应该？
looking for a way out
寻找出路
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
I'll ask someone to help you
我会请人帮助你
good father
好父亲
Don't worry when you come in
进来后不用担心
i will try my best
我会尽力而为
you are dreaming
你在做梦
Come to our company to receive business
来我公司接待业务
we have to follow the process
我们必须遵循流程
Don't expect me to open the back door for you
别指望我会为你开后门
you
你
Is it necessary to be so principled?
有必要这么有原则吗？
Just an internet administrator
你们
until this article
直到这篇文章
in this article
在这篇文章中
I understand
我懂了
You are a pit in my path
你是我前进路上的一个坑
How do you say this?
这话怎么说呢？
when i see you
当我看见你时
I know this won't work
我知道这样行不通
it's logical
这是符合逻辑的
Tianyang
天阳
This night is very simple
这个晚上很简单
Cook the pasta slowly
将意大利面慢慢煮
i can do anything
我什么事都能做
Lao Huang
老黄
I tell you
我告诉你
I can go in without you
没有你我也可以进去
this is correct
这是对的
There is no future based on relationships
建立在关系之上的未来是不存在的
let me help you
我来帮你
"Gao Tianyang."
“高天阳。”
come over
过来
Lao Huang
老黄
Unreliable
不可靠
now it's up to you
现在取决于你
depends on depends on
依赖于取决于
its power is internal
它的力量是内在的
Of course not difficult
当然不难
No
不
Isn't that all?
这还不是全部吗？
but i can't do that
但我不能那样做
Why
为什么
We doubt
我们怀疑
in the group
在群里
remember
记住
at any time
随时
And the people around you
还有你身边的人
any possibility
任何可能性
reveal your identity
暴露你的身份
it can't be there
它不可能在那里
according to your words
按照你的话
They're already inside
他们已经在里面了
Why do you want me to leave?
你为什么要我走？
Use night fog method
采用夜雾法
There are two plans
有两个计划
It's easy to get close to your uncle
很容易亲近你的叔叔
this is useful
这很有用
it's logical
这是符合逻辑的
What are we doing now?
我们现在干什么？
Haven't applied yet?
还没申请？
Enter according to your ability
根据你的能力进入
Not sure?
你不确定吗？
Okay, okay, no problem
好吧好吧没问题
This is good
这很好
for you
给你
Thanks
谢谢
what happened to you today
你今天怎么了
You are very happy
你很开心
You have received the interview notice
您已收到面试通知
Have you considered
你想好了吗
I don’t want Fang Lu to become a tragedy
我不想让方璐成为悲剧
it happens to us
它发生在我们身上
We don’t want Lao Huang
我们不要老黄
Become Mayor Fang
成为方市长
They took me to the water
他们带我去水边
They just admire Lao Huang
他们只是佩服老黄
if i don't go
如果我不去
They must be looking for someone else
他们一定是在寻找其他人
Instead of letting them deal with Lao Huang
而不是让他们去对付老黄
you'd better invite me
你最好邀请我
At least I won't hurt him
至少我不会伤害他
what if
如果什么
What if they ask you to take something away?
如果他们让你拿走东西怎么办
We will think of other ways
我们会想别的办法
Tianhai is not Macau
天海不是澳门
we have time to deal with them
我们有时间对付他们
Don't sigh
别叹息
I really have a way
我真的有方法
Don't worry
不用担心
correct
正确的
but now
但现在
a little
一点
have some problem
有点问题
What is the problem
有什么问题
interview
面试
tell me
告诉我
if i don't pass the interview
如果我没有通过面试
Both
两个都
They don't think I did it on purpose
他们不认为我是故意的
What do you think?
你觉得这怎么样？
i will do it for you
我会为你做
short-term training
短期培训
Are you OK?
你好吗？
Don't worry
不用担心
I'm arrogant
我很傲慢
Money has been transferred to your account
钱已经转入您的账户
what do you want
你想要什么
Any news on the high-speed rail auction?
高铁拍卖有什么消息吗
This is it
就是这个
most popular now
现在最流行
you have no right
你没有权利
Why are you not qualified?
为什么你没有资格？
strength
力量
you don't have that power
你没有那个权力
Your level is not special enough
你的水平不够特殊
Unable to obtain this information
无法获取该信息
i can pay
我可以付钱
Money is useless
钱没用
Buyer of this project
本项目买家
They are all whistleblowers
他们都是举报人
only
仅有的
in elite club
在精英俱乐部
you
你
can you come in?
你能进来吗？
Understood
明白了
Dear workers
尊敬的工人
after graduation
毕业之后
I do not have a job
我没有工作
Why
为什么
sorry
对不起
here
这里
I want to correct it
我想改正
No no no I don't have a job
不不不我没有工作
Instead, it’s a freelance career
相反，这是一个自由的职业
In fact, during this period
其实这段时间
I was watching before
我之前在看
Different career possibilities
不同职业的可能性
For example, I helped my friend
例如我帮助了我的朋友
Modify the program
修改程序
I created the program
我创建了程序
at the same time
同时
I got into the video game industry
我进入电子游戏行业
I got a good position
我得到了很好的位置
I
我
I love posting about my life
我喜欢发布我的生活
on the Internet
在互联网上
Me too
我也是
Excellent internet blog
优秀的互联网博客
How can you guarantee yourself?
你怎么能保证自己呢？
take on the job
承担这份工作
Although I am in this period
虽然我正处于这个时期
I do not have a job
我没有工作
but
但
This sense of unknown about tomorrow
这种对明天的未知感
it made me get used to being hungry
它让我习惯了饥饿
I like to face challenges
我喜欢面对挑战
I don't
我，不
betray
背叛
on your face
在你的脸上
But these years
但这些年
It makes me become an independent person
它让我成为一个有主见的人
good problem solver
善于解决问题的人
OK
好的
Do you have any other questions?
你还有其他问题吗
Do you want to ask me?
你想问我吗？
nature
自然
I am very interested
我很感兴趣
your corporate culture
您的企业文化
our company
我们公司
although
尽管
old company
老公司
but
但
I hear a lot from you
我从你那里听到了很多
I know
我知道
What is your company culture?
您的公司文化是
Collaboration, challenge, responsibility, creativity
协作、挑战、责任、创造力
Accidentally
意外地
I have experienced it all
我有这一切的经历
I like you
我喜欢你
you don't have a job
你没有工作
maybe you can
也许你可以
positive energy
正能量
Astonishing
惊人的
The teacher taught very well
老师教得很好
i think your photo
我认为你的照片
should be designed for you
应该为你设计
design
设计
follow me
跟我来
What's your photo?
你的照片是什么？
Quickly
迅速地
Are my photos bad?
我的照片不好吗？
No
不
Jihai Biological Group
集海生物集团
He is very talented in the industry
他在行业里很有才华
Here he loves talent
在这里他热爱才华
respect science
尊重科学
You are open to new ideas
你善于接受新想法
Hospital
医院
Per year
每年
It will be published in an international scientific journal
它将发表在国际科学期刊上
and i know
而且我知道
Then your hospital
那你的医院
ready to carry
准备好携带
some new products
一些新产品
system
系统
will be updated
将会被更新
System improvements
系统改进
This is my area of ​​expertise
这是我擅长的领域
if there is a chance
如果有机会的话
work hard here
在这里努力工作
and prove it
并证明这一点
expensive
昂贵的
i hope i have a chance
我希望我有机会
stand up
挺身而出
with everyone
与大家
Thanks
谢谢
I went for an interview today
我今天去面试了
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
no problem
没问题
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
What is his position?
他的立场是什么？
It means she is worried
说明她很担心
Actually I think
其实我觉得
Yaoyao has the desire to survive
瑶瑶有求生的欲望
Do you want to think about it?
你想不想想一下？
for it to come
为了让它到来
It's none of your business
这不关你的事
if
如果
the two of us
我们两个
We are united
我们团结一线
maybe today
也许今天
It won't be like this tomorrow
明天不是这样的
Why you
为什么你
don't believe her
不要相信她
I'm not targeting her
我不是针对她
hidden battle
隐藏的战斗
very complicated
非常复杂
you are our men
你们是我们的男人
You are a spy too
你也是间谍
you can work for us
你可以为我们工作
you can work for night mist
你可以为夜雾工作
Yaoyao too
瑶瑶也是
Identity is the biggest change
身份是最大的改变
in battle
战斗中
If one day
如果有一天
I find
我发现
Your loved one becomes a spy
你所爱的人变成了间谍
what to do
该怎么办
impossible
不可能的
You may have noticed this before
您之前可能已经注意到这一点
if you become a spy
如果你成为间谍
she became a spy
她成了一名间谍
save her
救救她
How can I save her?
我该如何拯救她？
make her confess
让她坦白
Send her to jail.
把她送进监狱。
Detailed analysis
细节分析
I have no choice now
我现在没有办法了
Give you a clear answer
给你一个明确的答案
I just want to ask you
我只想问你
Does Yaoyao still have a chance?
瑶瑶还有机会吗
Yes
是的
when
什么时候
I have no feelings for you
我对你没有感情
Why
为什么
exist
在
according to feeling
根据感觉
Untrustworthy
不可信任
Sister Shi said
石姐说
Your workers are human beings too
你们的工人也是人
How can a person have no feelings?
一个人怎么可能没有感情呢？
Don't get emotionally involved
不要投入感情
at work
在上班
I think I can't do it
我想我做不到
I think Sister Shi is good
我觉得石姐不错
tell her
告诉她
Be careful when performing tasks
执行任务时要小心
how do you know
你怎么知道
I went to work
我去干活了
if she is free
如果她有空的话
This is the working order
这是工作顺序
careful
小心
don’t worry
别担心
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
I need your help
我需要你的帮助
Dear workers
尊敬的工人
do something
做某事
Wow that
哇那个
Huang Zicheng
黄子成
do something
做某事
everything is ready
一切都准备好了
let's go
我们走吧
Verified
已验证
No verification rights
无验证权
The current task has been completed
当前任务已完成
No authority to verify
无权核实
The task has started
任务已经开始
So it cannot be verified
所以无法验证
can you find it
你能找到吗
Who accepted this mission?
谁接受了这个任务？
accomplish
实现
did you see
你有没有看到
the brunette
那个黑发女人
It's Mr. Zhang
是张先生
don't let her notice you
别让她注意到你
Where is my gear?
我的装备在哪里？
They all belong to Jiang Xiaohua
都是姜小花的
Jiang Xiaohua
蒋晓华
Where are you
你在哪
Don't panic
不要恐慌
I'm here
我在这
I will add a hidden phrase for you
我会为你添加一个隐藏短语
your external assistant
您的外部助理
You can only hold on for one minute
你只能坚持一分钟
I have made progress
我已经进步了
Now you can hold on for three minutes
现在你可以坚持三分钟
OK
好的
No one now
现在没人
find out where you are
找出你在哪里
you have it now
你现在拥有了
Just three minutes
只需三分钟
Leave now, it's time
现在离开，是时候了
don't let her find out
别让她发现
science
科学
I'll show you your eyes again
我会再次向你展示你的眼睛
Astonishing
惊人的
Appearance is gone
外表消失了
Did you find this agreement online?
你在网上找到这个协议了吗？
almost
几乎
Orphanage
孤儿院
Upgrade defense system
升级防御系统
Why is there an outside assistant?
怎么会有外面的助理
This opponent is very strong
这个对手很强
There are no rules in sports
运动没有规则
Very random
随机性很强
I don't know what he does
我不知道他做什么
you should always be careful
你应该随时小心
OK
好的
he is a beginner
他是个初学者
how
如何
to the club
到俱乐部
It must be Mr. Zhang calling him
一定是张先生在叫他
Can you
你可以吗
Can you find it?
你能找到吗？
The amount of information I have now is very limited
我现在掌握的信息量非常有限
We have to think of another way
我们必须想别的办法
This person's level of pretentiousness is very low.
这人的装逼水平很低
Obviously he is not a professional
明显他不是专业人士
I will nominate someone for you
我会为你提名一个人
we must find
我们必须找到
who is he
他是谁
Jiang Xiaohua
蒋晓华
she is just like you
她就像你一样
They are all hackers
他们都是黑客
I'm not a hacker
我不是黑客
I just do technical work
我只是从事技术工作
Isn't this the same thing?
这不是同一件事吗？
we can find that person
我们可以找到那个人
Isn't that all?
这还不是全部吗？
Jiang Xiaohua
蒋晓华
Stronger than stone
比石头还坚固
I assume you're passionate about technology
我认为你热衷于技术
in technology
在科技方面
But for the sake of relationship
但为了关系
We will never be older than her
我们绝对不会比她大
Can she agree?
她能同意吗？
Do you have a girlfriend
你有女朋友吗
What's your job
你做什么工作
you should love like you
你应该像你一样去爱
she looks well educated
她看起来很有教养
do not bother me
别打扰我
No
不
I'll go there directly
我会直接去那里
you will definitely ask
你肯定会问
so
所以
Introduce her to clients
将她介绍给客户
you have no money
你没有钱
Exchange equipment information with others
与他人交换装备信息
We can't let people waste their efforts
我们不能让人们白费力气
if you can find it
如果你能找到它
Give her all the equipment
把所有的装备都给她
Then I agree on her behalf
那么我就代表她同意
Why do I feel this way?
为什么我有这样的感觉？
you are selling information
你在卖信息
In the private world of workers
在工人的私人世界里
Isn’t this just information exchange?
这不就是信息交换吗？
Or let it go
或者放手吧
Lure Jiang Xiaohua
引诱姜小花
what do you look like?
你长的怎样？
are you serious?
你是认真的？
I have sent the data to your email
我已将数据发送至您的邮箱
So fast
这么快
He is a rookie player
他是一名新秀球员
no fakes
没有假货
It is not difficult to investigate
调查起来并不困难
Let's add friends
我们来添加好友吧
no need
没有必要
I will not friend clients
我不会与客户加好友
Did you discover it
你发现了吗
Yes
是的
That's the person
就是那个人
How did you find out?
你是怎么发现的？
Jiang Xiaohua is really amazing
姜小花真的很厉害
These teachers are in the game
这些老师在游戏中
Stronger than I expected
比我预想的要强
But as long as the data warehouse
但只要数据仓库
in data store
在数据存储中
i can find his identity
我可以找到他的身份
Aren’t you also a computer expert?
您不也是计算机专家吗？
She's just more talented than me
她只是比我更有天赋而已
But in fact
但实际上
Private Worker's Mission
私人工人的使命
it is hidden
它被隐藏了
These three are suitable
这三个适合
Picture after return
退货后的图
Let me compare again
我再比较一下
no need
没有必要
It's him
是他
laila
莱拉
French
法语
This person works in France
此人在法国工作
In France
在法国
working, busy
在工作，在忙
international consulting firm
国际咨询公司
He found Mr. Zhang
他找到了张先生
It is clear
很明显
to steal
为了偷窃
High Speed ​​Rail Auction Card USA
高铁拍卖卡美国
But these night fogs
但这些夜雾
Why work with the company?
为什么要与公司合作？
Stealing trade secrets
窃取商业秘密
No
不
Not a simple trade secret
不简单的商业秘密
I tell you
我告诉你
Traveling abroad by high-speed rail
乘坐高铁出国
To enhance the country’s image
旨在提升国家形象
improve international relations
改善国际关系
such responsibility
这样的责任
You are like a foreign spy organization
你们就像国外的间谍组织
you have tried your best
你已经尽力了
we press
我们压
This is an excellent product
这是一款优秀的产品
first
首先
he can get
他可以获得
Commercial interests
商业利益
second
第二
he can stop
他可以停下来
our excellent company
我们优秀的公司
our international image
我们的国际形象
To them
对他们来说
Why don't you do this?
你为什么不这样做呢？
after that
在那之后
I will follow
我将按照
with the security department
与保安部门
Negotiate
洽谈
let
让
Technology Department
技术部
to their secret department
到他们的秘密部门
for covert investigations
用于秘密调查
Just make sure
只要确保
in
里面
Tian Yang
田阳
Special attention should be paid to
应特别注意
Employees who can communicate
能够沟通的员工
do not leave
不要离开
don't leave anything
不要留下任何东西
No evidence
没有证据
Understood
明白了
Incidentally
顺便一提
Where is Wu Xi?
吴曦呢？
How is this going
这是怎么回事
I'm ready
我准备好了
We can go in tomorrow
我们明天就可以进去
in a car club
在汽车俱乐部里
for covert investigations
用于秘密调查
welcome
欢迎
Is this Miss Wu?
这是吴小姐吗？
Yes
是的
welcome
欢迎
I'm customer service
我是客服
(prohibit).
（禁止）。
do you have?
你有吗？
Automotive Design Workshop
汽车设计工作坊
Yes
是的
We are renovating the cart workshop
我们正在改造推车车间
He is the most professional in Tianhai
是天海最专业的
take me to see
带我去看看
OK
好的
What do you think?
你觉得这怎么样？
Waiting downstairs
在楼下等候
I will register you
我会为你注册
OK
好的
Come on, sign up
来吧，报名吧
you are the coach here
你是这里的教练
transfer
换车
Where do you usually hang out?
你通常去哪里玩？
I just came back from abroad
我刚从国外回来
Do You have a Car
你有车吗
your height
你的身高
you can ride more
你可以多骑
Coaching level here
教练级别在这里
Is this good?
这个好吗？
Have you attended this major before?
您之前参加过该专业吗？
Coach Xiao
肖教练
become
变得
come over
过来
Completed operations
已完成的操作
Have we met before?
我们以前见过吗？
I do not think so
我不这么认为
my sisters
我的姐妹
Coach Xiao
肖教练
.We are highly skilled
.我们技术精湛
Modify God
修改神
my sisters
我的姐妹
This is it
就是这个
factory
工厂
front rail
前轨
Do you have any opinion?
你有什么意见？
Is this good?
这个好吗？
OK
好的
here
这里
Help yourself
帮助自己
Mr. Yang
杨先生
Okay, you're here
好吧，你来了
my sisters
我的姐妹
CPR 650
心肺复苏 650
What's the coach's name?
教练叫什么名字？
What's his name
他叫什么名字
Xiao Yi
肖毅
Coach Xiao
肖教练
Do I bring a driver?
我带司机吗？
No
不
he is a consultant
他是一名顾问
Technical Adviser
技术顾问
Really good
真的很棒
it says
它说
He used to be a professional driver
他之前是一名职业司机
Have you ever ridden a ninja?
你骑过忍者吗？
ninja
忍者
my sisters
我的姐妹
The bicycle coach Xiao rides
肖教练骑的自行车
Too much
太多了
it's logical
这是符合逻辑的
Do you have an auto shop?
你们有汽车商店吗？
Yes
是的
There
那里
let's go
我们走吧
Sister, let me show you
姐姐我给你看看
OK
好的
Sister, this is our store
姐姐，这是我们店
Many families don’t have a car shop
许多家庭没有汽车店
They parked their car here
他们把车停在这里
Sister, what are you looking for?
姐姐你在找什么？
I want to see
我想看看
in any form
以任何形式
I don't want to be like them
我不想像他们一样
OK
好的
watch whatever you want
随心所欲地观看
I'll get you a glass of water
我给你倒杯水
Thanks
谢谢
Okay, go to work
好吧，去上班吧
I gonna go see
我去看看
sorry
对不起
OK
好的
I haven't eaten your food for a long time
我好久没吃你做的饭了
Gao Tianyang eats a lot
高天阳吃的很多
It has been a long time
已经很久了
I didn't ride your bike
我没有骑你的自行车
Do you think we are here to collect the sea?
你以为我们是来集海的吗？
Have you changed?
你变了吗？
slightly different
稍微不一样
I thought you were used to it
我以为你已经习惯了
Are you used to it?
你习惯了吗？
Still tired?
还是累了？
You mean work?
你是说工作吗？
or our relationship
或者我们的关系
I think you like this job
我认为你喜欢这份工作
I think you lack new feelings
我觉得你缺乏新的感觉
your new mission
你的新使命
He asked me to put out the fire
他让我把火扑灭
Do not say
不要说
this is good job
这是好工作
I will look forward to
我会期待